Lloyd: So now that you've
completed session three it's
time to complete the relevant
section of the assessment booklet.
So if you open your assessment booklet
and scroll down to section three, and
this section is about Understanding
Coding Acronyms and Terminology.
And again, at the top, there are learning
objectives that you will meet in this
section, but more importantly, the
location in the course  materials if
you need to refer back to assist you
with answering any of the questions.
So for question one, you have again
been asked to use the code, an example
of code that was provided from session
two, it's asking you to describe
what is meant by a unit of code?
And it's asking you up here, it's seeing
if you can identify a unit of code.
So where is the unit of code within there?
And in the box below,
describe what is meant...
so what is a unit of code
in relation to the program?
The programming language?
For question two, it's asking
you to list the characteristics
of dry and wet code and explain
the differences between the two.
So again, you can refer back to
the course materials to assist you
with this, but the question is...
so dry code characteristics,
so what are they?
Wet code characteristics -- what are they?
And what is the difference
between the two different types?
For question three, it's asked you to do
a little bit of research and it's asking
you to find programs that have been
written in open source and closed source.
So, using the internet there's numerous
examples on there of the different
programs that have been written with
the different types of source code.
If you do utilise any evidence from the
internet to support your answer, make
sure that you reference where you obtained
that information from within the box.
So once you've done that, and you're happy
with everything, I'd recommend checking
all through the unit two assessment
booklet, carry out a spelling and
grammar check, proofread your responses.
And if you're happy that everything's
okay, save the document and you can
then submit that to your tutor for
marking and move on to unit three.